Connecticut Citizens Action Group Records 1987.0024
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series XVIII: 1999 Addition, undated, 1970-1998
  - Employee Retirement Income Security Act, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4566)
  - Center for Insurance Research, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4567)
  - 1995 State Sessions, 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 4568)
  - the "State" of CT Health - DI notes, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4569)
  - OMCA/Rowland Budget, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4570)
  - OMCA Advisory Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 4571)
  - OMCA Advisory Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 4572)
  - Gunther's Reincarnation, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4573)
  - Johnson, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4574)
  - 6th CD - News Clips, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4575)
  - 5th CD - Action Planning, 1993-1995 (Box 137, Folder 4576)
  - Danbury Action - 29 August, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4577)
  - Families U.S.A., 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 4578)
  - Female Health Campaign, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4579)
  - Connecticut Choice Coalition, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4580)
  - Female Health, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4581)
  - United Automobile Workers, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4582)
  - National Citizen Action, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 4583)
  - Children, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4584)
  - To Do/Meeting Notes, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4585)
  - Citizen Action Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 4586)
  - Medicaid and Managed Care, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4587)
  - Dear Newt Gingrich, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4588)
  - Consumer Guides - MC, undated (Box 137, Folder 4589)
  - Lead (metal) - Info, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4590)
  - Legislative Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 137, Folder 4591)
  - HCAC/State Stuff, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4592)
  - Health Care Authority, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4593)
  - HCAC: Health Care Access Commission, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4594)
  - Catholic Hospital Association Health Care Proposal, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4595)
  - CT HCAC Report, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4596)
  - Long Term Care Coalition, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4597)
  - Health Care Strategy Group, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4598)
  - Nation Health Care Articles (Market), 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4599)
  - HCFA Agendas, 1992-1993 (Box 137, Folder 4600)
  - HCFA Postcard Campaign, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4601)
  - HCFA Actions, undated (Box 137, Folder 4602)
  - Out of State/National, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4603)
  - Health Link, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4604)
  - Polling - Budget, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4605)
  - Community Works, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4606)
  - Press List, undated (Box 137, Folder 4607)
  - Pharmacists, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 4608)
  - AETNA, 1995-1996 (Box 137, Folder 4609)
  - Speakers - Health Care, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4610)
  - Developing the Action Network, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4611)
  - Local Campaigns, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4612)
  - Corporate Campaigns, undated (Box 137, Folder 4613)
  - Insurance Research, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4614)
  - Labor Work Group, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4615)
  - Health Care - Electoral, 1994 (Box 137, Folder 4616)
  - CBIA, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4617)
  - Massachusetts, undated (Box 137, Folder 4618)
  - New York Health Care, 1993-1994 (Box 137, Folder 4619)
  - Maine Health Care, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4620)
  - Tennessee Health Care, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4621)
  - Hawaii Health Care, 1992 (Box 137, Folder 4622)
  - Vermont Health Care, 1992
  - Chicago, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4623)
  - Illinois Health Care, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4624)
  - Maine Campaign Finance and Health Care, undated (Box 137, Folder 4625)
  - New York HCFA, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4626)
  - TennCare, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4627)
  - State Materials - Gunther, etc., undated (Box 137, Folder 4628)
  - Health Care Bill Information, 1993 (Box 137, Folder 4629)
  - Insurance Committee, undated (Box 137, Folder 4630)
  - Contact Lists, 1991 (Box 137, Folder 4631)
  - Single-Payer Press Conference, 1995 (Box 137, Folder 4632)
  - Polluters in Connecticut, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 4633)
  - Zip Code List, undated (Box 138, Folder 4634)
  - Seymore, 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 4635)
  - Gasoline Market, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 4636)
  - CRRA, 1980-1989 (Box 138, Folder 4637)
  - Medical Wastes, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 4638)
  - Personal Financial Information - Peter Rawson, 1991 (Box 138, Folder 4639)
  - EPA and Other Highway Documents, 1984-1988 (Box 138, Folder 4640)
  - Expressway Materials, 1983-1984 (Box 138, Folder 4641)
  - Route 6, 1989 (Box 138, Folder 4642)
  - Expressway - Legal Documents, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 4643)
  - Expressway - Events, 1984 (Box 138, Folder 4644)
  - Expressway - Group, 1983-1985 (Box 138, Folder 4645)
  - Expressway Materials, 1979-1985 (Box 138, Folder 4646)
  - Environmental Policy Publication, 1991-1992 (Box 138, Folder 4647)
  - Interstate 84, 1975-1979 (Box 138, Folder 4648)
  - Highway Materials, 1985-1988 (Box 138, Folder 4649)
  - I-84 Strategy Committee Meetings, 1982-1984 (Box 138, Folder 4650)
  - I-84 Hampton/Scotland Interchange, 1982 (Box 138, Folder 4651)
  - Highway News Clippings, 1980-1988 (Box 138, Folder 4652)
  - Grassrotts Ecology Newsletters, 1984-1994 (Box 138, Folder 4653)
  - Candidates and Elected Town Officials, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 4654)
  - Economy, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 4655)
  - Citizen Action - Environment and National Activities, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 4656)
  - S.O.S. Active Work, 1993-1994 (Box 138, Folder 4657)
  - Gubernatorial Election, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 4659)
  - S.O.S. Meeting Materials, 1993 (Box 138, Folder 4660)
  - W.R.A.P. Meeting Materials, undated (Box 138, Folder 4661)
  - Route 6, 1994 (Box 138, Folder 4663)
  - Miles Rappaport for Congress Bumper Stickers, undated (Box 139, Folder 4664)
  - CCAG Consumer Handbooks, 1991-1997 (Box 139, Folder 4665)
  - Staff and Board Planning Retreat, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 4666)
  - 15th Annual Connecticut Lobbying Conference, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 4667)
  - Peer White Paper: A Friend in High Places, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 4668)
  - Hartford Courant Health Care Articles, 1992-1994 (Box 139, Folder 4669)
  - Color of Money: Campaign Contributions and Race, undated (Box 139, Folder 4670)
  - CCAG Report, undated, 1981-1990 (Box 139, Folder 4671)
  - Citizen Action News, 1985 (Box 139, Folder 4672)
  - Northeast Utilities Service Company Correspondence, 1996 (Box 139, Folder 4673)
  - Canvass Aids, 1981 (Box 139, Folder 4674)
  - CCAG History, 1991 (Box 139, Folder 4677)
  - CCAG News Report, 1972-1980 (Box 139, Folder 4678)
  - CCAG Ad Books, 1982-1988 (Box 139, Folder 4679)
  - CCAG 10th Anniversary Celebration, 1980 (Box 139, Folder 4680)
  - CCAG 20th Anniversary Celebration, 1990 (Box 139, Folder 4681)
  - How SBC Devoured Pac Bell, 1998 (Box 139, Folder 4682)
  - Save Our State Coalition, Inc., 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4683)
  - CRRA Materials, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4684)
  - Environment Press Releases, Statements, etc., 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4685)
  - Incineration, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4686)
  - Lead Poisoning, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4687)
  - Why Global Warming Spells Rising Global Tensions, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4688)
  - Low-Level Radioactive Waste, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4689)
  - Mailing List on Environment, undated (Box 140, Folder 4690)
  - Fact Sheets, undated (Box 140, Folder 4691)
  - WERF, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4692)
  - SCRRA Trash Deal, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4693)
  - Jetport, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4694)
  - Transportation Center Corruption, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4695)
  - S.O.S. Jetport Rally, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4696)
  - Global Warming and Clean Air, 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4697)
  - Waste Management Inc., 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4698)
  - Hazardous Waste Documents, 1983 (Box 140, Folder 4699)
  - Soil Burning Plants, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4700)
  - Energy Conservation and Efficiency, 1991-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4701)
  - Nuclear Weapons, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4702)
  - Cleaner Vehicles, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4703)
  - EPA Report "Improved Public Transportation, undated (Box 140, Folder 4704)
  - Jetport Work in Progress, 1991-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4705)
  - Jetport Materials, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4706)
  - Jetport Materials, 1971-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4707)
  - Transportation and Clean Air, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4708)
  - Public Transportation and the 1990 Clean Air Act, 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4709)
  - DEP Clean Air Network, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4710)
  - Transportation and Clean Air Materials, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4711)
  - Route 6, 1989-1991 (Box 140, Folder 4712)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration, Lisba, Middletown, CT, 1990-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4713)
  - Solid Waste - Windham Energy Recovery Facility (WERF)
  - Solid Waste - Summary: 1992 Proposed RCRA Amendments (Box 140, Folder 4715)
  - Solid Waste - Lisbon Incinerator, PEP Policies, Press Conference, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4716)
  - Solid Waste - Lisbon Briefs, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4717)
  - Solid Waste - Incinerator, Ash, undated (Box 140, Folder 4718)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration: Need Issues, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4719)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration: General, undated (Box 140, Folder 4720)
  - Solid Waste - Recycling: General, 1992-1993 (Box 140, Folder 4721)
  - Solid Waste - Recycling: Need for Enforcement Authority, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4722)
  - Solid Waste - Household and Other Hazardous Waste, 1992 (Box 140, Folder 4722)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration and Recycling, 1991 (Box 140, Folder 4724)
  - Solid Waste - Incinerators: National, undated (Box 140, Folder 4725)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration, fees, etc., 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4727)
  - Solid Waste - Incineration, Lisbon, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4728)
  - Solid Waste - '93 Attempted Legislation, General Assembly, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4729)
  - Mean B. Sus - Environmental Products, 1993 (Box 140, Folder 4730)
  - Notes, administrative records, publications, clippings, manuscripts, 1986-1991 (Box 1999_1, Folder data_value_missing_9311c0bf94018dcad44d563860da6d27)
    [Subjects include: Medicaid, aids, labor, legislation, long-term care, HCFA.]
  - Clippings, notes, administrative records, correspondence, manuscripts, 1988-1989 (Box 1999_2, Folder data_value_missing_592c818728018a8c638ec8b6022a48d0)
    [Subjects include: ash landfills, recycling, enforcement, solid waste, I-84.]
  - Administrative records, clippings, manuscripts, notes, correspondence, publications, 1991-1996 (Box 1999_3, Folder data_value_missing_45f805671ccf366dc522dfc07ef04ac9)
    [Subjects include: health care, McDermott Congress, NECARC, Mental Health Associations of CT, ERISA, Resource Inventory.]
  - Notes, administrative records, clippings, 1991-1996 (Box 1999_4, Folder data_value_missing_ce637e1c08d8dbdbdea07a5ff9277c2c)
    [Subjects include: children, speakers, state healthcare updates, developing the A.N., Citizen-Action, health, Pizza Hut, Medicaid, AETNA, Second District, transition proposals, state sessions, Christopher Shays, Barbara Kennelly, OHCA.]
  - Clippings, administrative records, legal documents, financial records, publications, manuscripts, undated (Box 1999_5, Folder data_value_missing_6f5871d9e6e6add6e709bfe007fd76b0)
    [Subjects include: medical wastes, Mary B. Walton, I-84, CHPEA.]
  - Fliers, publications, manuscripts, clippings, notes, administrative records, 1970-1998 (Box 1999_6, Folder data_value_missing_62450c8dbef83e463a153fa7cc4ded1b)
    [Subjects include: reports, newsletters, and ad books.]
  - Notes, clippings, legal documents, administrative records, 1990-1993 (Box 1999_7, Folder data_value_missing_635e273e10de420ac6187b2e92da0140)
    [Subjects include: environment, energy, Route 6, public transportation, jetport, recycling, Lisbon, 1990 Clean Air Act, mercury, New Jersey, solid waste, lead poisoning.]
  - Publications, fliers, notes, administrative records, clippings, correspondence, manuscripts, books, photographs, 1990-1995 (Box 1999_8, Folder data_value_missing_b473b8486d5db8972095b4783a89574b)
    [Subjects include: progressive policy, Stamford, enforcement, state of regulation, CT Dept. of Health Services, Spanish Class, Task Force Report, Lead Inspector Training, Lead Poisoning, New Haven, protocol, children, state health.]
  - Publications, manuscripts, notes, administrative records, 1991 (Box 1999_9, Folder data_value_missing_ab9ed0f06f9ce9b5ba2a09c267f7c0e4)
    [Subjects include: auto insurance, auto background, auto task force, House Dem. Operations Dept., Citizen Action, CIT, Common Cause - Campaign Finance Reform]
  - Publications, manuscripts, administrative records, notes, photographs, fliers, 1989-1990 (Box 1999_10, Folder data_value_missing_9955aef641238b1ffb3fcb784661fe87)
    [Subjects include: phone canvassers, recycling, staff meetings, sales, agriculture, citizen outreach, East Hampton.]
  - Administrative records, books, fliers, 1993 (Box 1999_11, Folder data_value_missing_cc1a1128427717a56fa3a05e3d091ea3)
    [Subjects include: Local Trash Flights, Waterbury, Uninsured Motorists, no fault auto insurance (Maine), Coalition for Insurance Justice, trial lawyers, civil justice.]
  - Administrative records, notes, clippings, correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 1999_12, Folder data_value_missing_8dd47a528fdf07b3a9524dbe3d06d8e9)
    [Subjects include: nataional health care, Pepper commission, labor, Ohio bill, Russo bill, NCA, NH healthcare, VT healthcare, NY healthcare, CT healthcare, consumer reports, CA/NHCC memoranda.]
  - Administrative records, notes, 1992 (Box 1999_13, Folder data_value_missing_9425e000f36242cfecf10942737295e6)
    [Subjects include: HCAC, "Healthy Steps," meetings, workplans, Health Access Comm.]
  - Notes, fliers, administrative records, books, clippings, correspondence, 1985-1991 (Box 1999_14, Folder data_value_missing_3897c301171b18f4cece692eebcc36a3)
    [Subjects include: Oakdale, CT, Fairfield, CT, radon gas, solid/hazardous waste management, toxic air, global warming, Citizen Action Air report, environment, Gales Ferry, LA reports, benzene, vapor locks, wetlands, Windham trash contacts, styrofoam, CA energy.]
  - Legal documents, administrative records, correspondence, financial records, notes, 1987-1990 (Box 1999_15, Folder data_value_missing_0555bedf74a21a195e019fcd113749c1)
    [Subjects include: "unisured," hospital rates, BRC: Lewin PA, BRC: Progressive Lane, Lewin cons. Barbara Kennelly, blue ribbon, CA HC, Citizen Action/NHCG, HCFA.]
  - Administrative records, financial records, clippings, notes, 1991-1996 (Box 1999_16, Folder data_value_missing_aafcdabd837cd60399e17b13d5fedda5)
    [Subjects include: 30th birthday, CA lobby, HCFA, workshops, MED Mal, Hillary mtg, M/M, families USA, cost shifting, children, Medicaid, corporate medicine, Maine, managed care, long-term care.]
  - Books, notes, clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 1999_17, Folder data_value_missing_a5a58a1395b09903420aa9bd9986bafe)
    [Subjects include: Blue Cross/Anthem--Ohio, BC/BS CT by-laws, Anti-BC/BS, insurance.]
- Series XIX: 2006 Addition (Health care for all), 1987-2002
  - Financial records, publications, books, administrative records, notes, 1998-2002 (Box 2006_1, Folder data_value_missing_c8439b7b47b5cffc0ecdc5d73888377f)
    [Subjects include: Yale study, statistics on medicare, health care, Husky Focus Groups and uninsured.]
  - Correspondence, administrative records, notes, 1987-1997 (Box 2006_2, Folder data_value_missing_aed73c69e2d4e0c3c89f244f40b7fdef)
    [Subjects include: HCFA, care pools, HC systems, Congress, Endorsements.]
  - Administrative records, fliers, notes, legal documents, financial records, photographs, clippings, 1990-1996 (Box 2006_3, Folder data_value_missing_ad3d9079883b779881f7ac1bf717a2da)
    [Subjects include: HC, HCAC, HCFA, Hartford.]
  - Notes, administrative records, 1997-2001 (Box 2006_4, Folder data_value_missing_2d9a471a19fe4230f34e61ca07d30467)
    [Subjects include: CT Assoc. for Human Services, Children's Health, NAIC/CCRG, Legislation, HCFA.]
  - Administrative records, correspondence, notes, 1998-2000 (Box 2006_6, Folder data_value_missing_6528a40f32c88c34903cf46b39c67eaa)
    [Subjects include: mental health, tax breaks, lawsuits, HMO reform, confidentiality, AETNA-U.S.]
  - Publications, financial records, administrative records, notes, 1998-2000 (Box 2006_8, Folder data_value_missing_4b7deedf5abea3f16bbdf77719510461)
    [Subjects include: money, hunger, insurance, politics, conversion and communication benefits, Medigap, Nancy Johnson, HMO, Bradley/ Gore, polling, Mt. Sinai Hospital.]
  - Administrative records, publications, financial records, notes, 1999-2000 (Box 2006_9, Folder data_value_missing_6bbc362419b4cf8be431704a7d6d1538)
    [Subjects include: RX working group, education, New Haven, Maine legislation, drugs, Public Welfare Foundation, Massachusetts, DSS Pharmacy, Families USA, New York, H.C.]
  - Administrative records, notes, books, 1996-2000 (Box 2006_10, Folder data_value_missing_f9400af141b7e741c6ebfd02fe50223a)
    [Subjects include: Medicare beneficiaries, health, social security, advocates network, Families USA, Congressional meetings, Clinton Proposal, Nursing Home reform, Women's Health.]
  - Notes, correspondence, legal documents, financial records, administrative records, clippings, 1994-1999 (Box 2006_11, Folder data_value_missing_b7222d5ab0cd63e99591dc4dadbf54f5)
    [Subjects include: fundraising, election day, single payer, public welfare, Attorney General fraud, HCFA, ConnPACE, ConnMAP, NECARC, Conn. NARAL, small business, action line, League of Women's Voters, Kaiser Foundation.]
- Series XX: 2013 Addition, 1990-2010
  Scope and Content Note
  [Subjects Include]: Developement Plan
  - Manuscripts, Correspondence, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_1)
    [Subjects Include]: Connecticut Action Group flyers, News articles tittled "Report:Police Slow To Comply" and "Janitor Wants Mayor Held In Contempt", Basic Procedure for Corporate Contacts, Connecticut Action Group 1984 AD Book, A Proposal to Lynne Ide about Incorporation of the CCAG oil Co-op,Thank you letter from Christopher J. DODD, Connecticut Action Group News Letter, CCAG Holiday Auction Program Book,CCAG 1988 AD Book, 1991 CCAG Consumer HandBook, Original 1998 Ad Book, Orignal 1986 Ad Book,1989 Original Ad Book, Original 1988 Ad Book,20th Anniversary Program Book, CCAG 1987 Ad Book, Ad Book 1996 copy,1998 Ad book copy, CCAG 1985 Ad Book, CCAG 1999-2000 Program Book,CCAG 2003-2004 Consumer Handbook, CCAG 2000-2001 Consumer Handbook, 1983 Ad book Materials, 1992 consumer HandBook, 1991 Ad Book Originals,1997 Consumer Hand book ,1998 Ad Book Copy, 1996 Ad Book Copy, CCAG Little Red Song Book, CCAG Little Blue Song Book, CCAG Directory of Former Staff,30th Aniversary Sponsors, Annual Meet 1996,HCFA 1999 dues, 1999 Alaskan Rainforest Campaign,Music Fundraising, Other Organizations Program Books,Cigarette Tax, 1997 Environment Protection poll, Marketing Research, 1998 Working Families Poll, 1998 Managed Care Political Poll, 1998 Money in Politics Pol, Campuses 1994, 1999 Young people Social Security Poll, Medicate Polling, JRS Letter
  - Manuscrpits, Photographs, Correspondence, Fliers,Clippings, Publications, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_2)
    [subjects Include]:CCAG Holiday Auction Cards, Constitution of the International Union Book,CCAG 2001-2002 Program Book, Invitation to a reception for One Connecticut Action, Connecticut 2005- 2006 Directory Federal and State Elected Officials, CCAG Consumer Handbook 2002-2003, LEAP Annual Awards Dinner Book,David J. Frent Political American Auction Book, Celebrating Connecticut Womens Education & Legal Fund Book,Letter from Lynn W. Lyford to Members of the Standing Joint Committee on Human Services, CCAG Flyer ,CCAG "Protecting Our Democracy" flyer, CCAG 2002 Environmental Legislative Agenda,CCAG Special Campaign ,Flyer pertaining to Health Issue Priorities 2002, "The Excess Cost of the Bush Prescription Drug Plan in Connecticut",CCAG 2004 Holiday Auction Book, Hartfod Courant: "Leader For 'Six Pillars'", Coordinated Campaign, Connecticut Needs Publicly Financed Elections, Health Care For All Coalition, 2004-2005 CCAG Consumer HandBook, Letter inviting Mark Espinosa to place an ad in their ad book, CCAG Invitations to the Holiday Auction in 2005, Connecticut Citizens Action Group agenda for the 2005 connecticut state legislature, CCAG 2001 30th anniversary celebration program, Campaign for consumer protection,Auction 2002,Environment, National Committee to Preserve Social Security and Medicine, News Article, State of Connecticut Department Of Consumer Protection, I-84 fund,Sprague Fund, Memeber Articles, CCAG Board List, CCAG Past Bid List, The Swindells Charitable Foundation Trust 1998, Connecticut Decade of Business Tax Cuts, Public Assistance to Connecticut Business by Pual Kumar & Cynthia Ward, Rough Recovery: Connecticut Trend of Widening Economic Inequality by James Stodder, Coporate Responsibility and the Connecticut Economy, U.S Pirg Fact Sheet,Hartford Courant Article, Pledges, CCAG News paper,Mailing to All Pac Endorsed candidates, Voting Guides, Incinerators, Photographs, Tabacco Info, How SBC Devoured Pac Bell: Implications Of An SBC Takeover, (1985-1994) Swindells
  - Manuscripts,Correspondence, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_3)
    [Subjects Include ]: HUD Forms, Rescheduled Inspector Assessor,Eligibility Change, Lead Paint Hazardous Control Program, Insurance, Testing Protocols, Weekly Activity Report, Media Training, Lead Poisining Articles, Environment, Environment Binder full of articles from 1992-1999,CCAG Press,Tobacco taxes, Dishonorable Discharge Toxic Pollution of Connecticut Waters, LEAP 1998 Electoral Project,Media, Dirty Money: An analysis of campaign contributions and environmental enforcement by Eric Baily,Dirty Water Scoundrels, Consumer Federation of America: Excess Profits and The Impact of Competition on The Baby Bells,Snet-SBC Merger
  - Correspondence, Clippings,Fliers, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_4)
    [Subjects Include]: News Clippings, Campaign Finance Reform Press 1993-1994, CFR Press 1995, Media, Supervisory Meetings, Organizing A Social Change: A Manual For Activists in The 90's,CCAG 1999-2000 Program Book, Recall Rowland Flier, Civil Rights & Publicly Funded Elections: Transforming our Communities, Connecticut 2005-2006 Directory Federal and State Elected Official, Rowland-League Trading Cards,
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, Fliers, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_5)
    [Subjects Include]: Tobacco, Campaign Planning, 2000 Log of official State Staff, Article Publications, Color of Money, Contribution Limits, Ethics Municipal Codes, Media coverage, Power Point Presentation Campaign Finance Reform, Dodd Chris, Miscellaneous documents, Press 1994, Pac Lit Originals Senate, Captiol Investment: A Study Of Legislative Leadership PAC Fundraising
  - Manuscripts,Correspondence, 1990-2010 (Box 2013.0157_6)